A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1953-2004
Library of Virginia
- I. Commissioner's Correspondence, 1982-2004 (bulk 1995-2003)., Extent: 60 cubic feet (60 boxes). (Box 1-60)
  - 1999
    - Strategic Planning Initiatives (Box 28)
    - Tobacco Taskforce (Box 28)
    - Pesticides (Box 29)
    - Lawson, Marvin - Office of Pesticide Services (Box 29)
    - Pesticides Fees - Refund (Box 29)
    - Rogers, Alan - Product and Industry Standards (Box 29)
    - Eggborn, Phil - Plant and Pest Services (Box 29)
    - Sleight, Thomas - Director, Division of Marketing (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous - Division of Marketing (Box 29)
    - Commodity Services (Box 29)
    - Office of International Marketing (Box 29)
    - Strategic Planning Files from Don's Office (Box 29)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary (Box 29)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (1) (Box 29)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (2) (Box 29)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (3) (Box 29)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (4) (Box 30)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (1) (Box 30)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (2) (Box 30)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (3) (Box 30)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (4) (Box 30)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (5) (Box 30)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (6) (Box 30)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (7) (Box 30)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (8) (Box 30)
    - Suggested Responses (2) (Box 31)
    - Suggested Responses (3) (Box 31)
    - Suggested Responses (4) (Box 31)
    - Suggested Responses (5) (Box 31)
    - Suggested Responses (6) (Box 31)
  - 2000
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (3) (Box 32)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (4) (Box 32)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (5) (Box 32)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (6) (Box 32)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (7) (Box 32)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (8) (Box 32)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (9) (Box 32)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (10) (Box 33)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (11) (Box 33)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (1) (Box 33)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (2) (Box 33)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary (Box 33)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (3) (Box 33)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (2) (Box 33)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (1) (Box 33)
    - Blankenship, Donald G. (1) (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Commissioner's Office (Box 34)
    - Memos to SMT (Box 34)
    - Accomplishments - Governor (Box 34)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS (Box 34)
    - Arrington, Christina B., Internal Auditor (Box 34)
    - Dickinson, William P., Jr. (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Ag. Dev. Services (Box 34)
    - Kapelewski, Joseph (Box 34)
    - Jackson, Karen E. (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resource Office (Box 34)
    - Seward, Roy E. (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy, Planning and Research (Box 34)
    - Giles, Perida (Box 34)
    - Pugh, Sarah (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Ag. Stewardship (Box 34)
    - Lidholm, Elaine J. (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Communication and Media Relations (Box 34)
    - Adams, Sandy (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Administrative and Financial Services (Box 34)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (2) (Box 34)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (1) (Box 34)
    - Allgeier, Jerry (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Information Systems (Box 34)
    - Garey, Louis M. (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Facilities Management (Box 34)
    - Martin, Teddy R. (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Procurement (Box 34)
    - Kapelewski, Joseph (Finance Office) (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance Office (empty) (Box 34)
    - Sims, William D. (Box 34)
    - Suggested Response (1) (Box 35)
    - Suggested Response (2) (Box 35)
    - Suggested Response (3) (Box 35)
    - Suggested Response (4) (Box 35)
    - Suggested Response (5) (Box 35)
    - Suggested Response (6) (Box 35)
    - VDACS 2000 Legislation (Box 35)
    - 2000-2002 Budget Issues (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous - Animal Industry Services (Box 36)
    - Butts, Donald W. (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Protection (Box 36)
    - Office of Consumer Affairs Report on the Activities, 1999 (Box 36)
  - 2001
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (5) (Box 37)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (6) (Box 37)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (6) (Box 37)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (7) (Box 37)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (1) (Box 37)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (2) (Box 37)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (3) (Box 37)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary (Box 37)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (4) (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous - Commissioner's Office (Box 38)
    - Memos to the SMT (Box 38)
    - Arrington, Christina B., Internal Auditor (Box 38)
    - Dickinson, William P., Jr. (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Ag. Development Services (Box 38)
    - Office of Farmland Preservation (Box 38)
    - Jackson, Karen E. (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resource Office (Box 38)
    - Seward, Roy E. (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy, Planning and Research (Box 38)
    - Giles, Perida (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Ag. Stewardship (Box 38)
    - Pugh, Sarah (Box 38)
    - Lidholm, Elaine J. (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Communications and Media Relations (Box 38)
    - Adams, Sandra (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Administrative and Financial Services (Box 38)
    - Halblieb, Craig M. (2) (Box 38)
    - Halblieb, Craig M. (1) (Box 38)
    - Allgeier, Jerry (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Information Systems (Box 38)
    - Garey, Louis M. (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Facilities Management (Box 38)
    - Martin, Teddy R. (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Procurement (Box 38)
    - Kapelewski, Joseph, Finance Office (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance Office (Box 38)
    - Sims, William D. (Box 38)
  - 2002
    - Suggested Response (1) (Box 39)
    - Suggested Response (2) (Box 39)
    - Suggested Response (3) (Box 39)
    - Suggested Response (4) (Box 39)
    - Suggested Response (5) (Box 39)
    - Suggested Response (6) (Box 39)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (2) (Box 39)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (6) (Box 40)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (7) (Box 40)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (8) (Box 40)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (9) (Box 40)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (10) (Box 40)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (11) (Box 40)
    - Executive Agreement, Agency Head - J. Carlton Courter, III (Box 40)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (1) (Box 40)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (2) (Box 40)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (3) (Box 40)
    - Weekly Reports to Secretary (Box 40)
    - Governor Warner Transition (Box 41)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 41)
    - Homeland Security Grant (Box 41)
    - Horse Council, Virginia (Box 41)
    - Virginia Horticultural Council (Box 41)
    - Hot Line Cases (Box 41)
    - House of Representatives, US Congress (Box 41)
    - Land Use (Box 41)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of (Box 41)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) (Box 41)
    - Virginia Invasive Species Workgroup (Box 41)
    - Interior, US Dept. of (Box 41)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 41)
    - 2002 Legislative Guidelines (Box 41)
    - Legislative Proposals, 2002 (Box 41)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of (Box 41)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 41)
    - Migrant Workers (Box 41)
    - USDA National Organic Program (Box 41)
    - Perdue (Box 41)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 41)
    - Presentation to the House Appropriations Subcommittee, 5 February 2002 (Box 41)
    - Purcell, John B. (Box 41)
    - Ratmink (Box 41)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 41)
    - Senators (Box 41)
    - Report to the Senate Finance Committee (Box 41)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 41)
    - Sole Source (Box 41)
    - Southeastern Virginia Farmers Market Coop (Box 41)
    - State Police (Box 41)
    - Strategic Planning, 2002-2004 (Box 41)
    - Task Force - Food Safety (Box 41)
    - Supplier Diversity Program (Box 41)
    - Virginia Post Attack Economic Task Force (Box 41)
    - Technology, Secretary of (Box 41)
    - Tobacco (Box 41)
    - Tobacco Trust Certification Board (Box 41)
    - Minutes - Tobacco Idem. And Com. Rev. Commission (Box 41)
    - Travel, Blanket (Box 41)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 41)
    - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Rev. Com. (Box 41)
    - MOU - VDACS and Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission (Box 41)
    - USDA (2) (Box 41)
    - USDA (1) (Box 42)
    - VPI and SU (Box 42)
    - Water Plan (Box 42)
    - Wekert Bankruptcy Case (Box 42)
    - YMCA (Box 42)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council (Box 42)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 42)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 42)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 42)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board (Box 42)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board (Box 42)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board (Box 42)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 42)
    - NASDA (Box 42)
    - SASDA (Box 42)
    - SUSTA (Box 42)
    - State Fair (Box 42)
    - MOU - VDACS and VPI and SU (Box 42)
    - Performance Measures (Box 42)
    - Southeast Farmers Market (Box 42)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS (Box 42)
    - Accounts, Dept. of (Box 42)
    - Agenda - SMT (Box 42)
    - Agreement - Hydrilla Cooperative Project (Box 42)
    - Agreement - VDACS and Dept. of General Services (Consolidated Labs) (Box 42)
    - MOU - Geographic Information Systems (Box 42)
    - Apple Board, Virginia (Box 42)
    - Atlantic Rural Expo (Box 42)
    - Attorney General's Office (Box 42)
    - Audit - Food Safety Program (Box 42)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 42)
    - Internal Auditor, Dept. of (Box 42)
    - Awards Committee - VDACS (Box 42)
    - Business Resumption Plan (Box 42)
    - Charity Food Advisory Board (Box 42)
    - Chippokes Plantation Farm Foundation (Box 42)
    - Code Commission, Virginia (Box 42)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC) (Box 42)
    - Commission on Local Government (Box 42)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute (Box 42)
    - Comptrollers Office (Box 42)
    - Congressional Briefing Background (VDACS) (Box 42)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 42)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 42)
    - Dairy Compact (Box 42)
    - Dairymen's Association, Virginia (Box 42)
    - Delmarva Poultry (Box 42)
    - Lawson, Marvin, Office of Pesticide Services (Box 43)
    - Pesticide Fees - Refund (Box 43)
    - Rogers, Alan, Office of Product and Industry Standards (Box 43)
    - Fulgham, Frank, Office of Plant and Pest Services (Box 43)
    - Sleight, Thomas (Box 43)
    - Office of International Marketing (Box 43)
    - MOA - VDACS and Virginia-Maryland Reg. (Box 43)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (1) (Box 43)
    - Blankenship, Donald G. (Box 43)
    - Mulugeta, Markos (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous - Commissioner's Office (Box 43)
    - Memos - SMT (Box 43)
    - Dickinson, William P. (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous - Ag. Development (Box 43)
    - Office of Farmland Preservation (Box 43)
    - Arrington, Christina B., Internal Auditor (Box 43)
    - Jackson, Karen E. (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resource Office (Box 43)
    - Seward, Roy E. (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy, Planning and Research (Box 43)
    - Giles, Perida (Box 43)
    - Parker, Kiesha (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous - Ag. Stewardship (Box 43)
    - Lidholm, Elaine (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous - Communications and Media Relations (Box 43)
    - Adams, Sandra (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous - Administration and Financial Services (Box 43)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (2) (Box 43)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (1) (Box 43)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (2) (Box 43)
    - Allgeier, Jerry (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous - Information Systems (Box 44)
    - Garey, Louis (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous - Facilities Management (Box 44)
    - Martin, Teddy (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous - Procurement (Box 44)
    - Kapelewski, Jospeh, Finance Office (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance Office (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous - Animal Industry Services (Box 44)
    - Sims, William (Box 44)
    - Butts, Donald W. (Box 44)
    - Endangered Species (Box 44)
    - Office of Dairy and Food (Box 44)
    - Consumer Affairs Annual Report (Box 44)
    - Alvarez, Andy (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Protection (Box 44)
    - Pesticide (2) (Box 44)
    - Pesticide (1) (Box 44)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (5) (Box 44)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (4) (Box 44)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (3) (Box 45)
    - Suggested Response (7) (Box 45)
  - 2003
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Protection (Box 46)
    - Butts, Donald W. (Box 46)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (1) (Box 46)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (2) (Box 46)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (6) (Box 46)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (5) (Box 46)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (1) (Box 46)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (2) (Box 46)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (3) (Box 47)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (4) (Box 47)
    - Blankenship, Donald G. (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Commissioner's Office (Box 47)
    - Arrington, Christina B., Internal Auditor (Box 47)
    - Jackson, Karen E. (Box 47)
    - Office of Farmland Preservation (Box 47)
    - Dickinson, William P. (Box 47)
    - Memos - SMT (Box 47)
    - Seward, Roy E. (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resources (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Procurement (Box 47)
    - Martin, Teddy (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Facilities Management (Box 47)
    - Garey, Louis (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Information Systems (Box 47)
    - Allgeier, Jerry (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance Office (Box 47)
    - Kapelewski, Joseph, Finance Office (Box 47)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (3) (Box 47)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (2) (Box 47)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (1) (Box 47)
    - Adams, Sandra (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Communications and Media Relations (Box 47)
    - Lidholm, Elaine (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Ag. Stewardship (Box 47)
    - Parker, Keisha (Box 47)
    - Giles, Perida (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous - Office of Policy, Planning and Research (Box 47)
    - Suggested Response (1) (Box 48)
    - Suggested Response (2) (Box 48)
    - Suggested Response (3) (Box 48)
    - Suggested Response (4) (Box 48)
    - Suggested Response (5) (Box 48)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (7) (Box 48)
    - Weekly Repots to the Secretary (Box 48)
    - Lawson, Marvin (Box 49)
    - Fee Schedules - Division of Animal, Plant and Food Industry Services (Box 49)
    - Animal Pounds and Shelters (Box 49)
    - Office of Dairy and Food (Box 49)
    - Virginia Feed Law Issues (Box 49)
    - Alvarez, Andy, Consumer Affairs (Box 49)
    - Pesticide (4) (Box 49)
    - Pesticide (3) (Box 49)
    - Pesticide (2) (Box 49)
    - Pesticide (1) (Box 49)
    - Pesticide Fees - Refund (Box 49)
    - Rogers, Alan, Office of Product and Industry Standards (Box 49)
    - Report on Weights and Measures Fees (Box 49)
    - Fulgham, Frank M., Office of Plant and Pest Services (Box 49)
    - Endangered Species (Box 49)
    - Sleight, Thomas (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous - Division of Marketing (Box 49)
    - Brussells Office (empty) (Box 49)
    - Commodity Services (Box 49)
    - Grain Grading (empty) (Box 49)
    - Office of International Marketing (Box 49)
    - Fruit and Vegetable Fees (empty) (Box 49)
    - Peanut Inspection Fee (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous, 1996-2001
    - Plasticulture - Eastern Shore Vegetable and Shellfish Grower Advisory Committee (Box 50)
    - Eastern Shore Vegetable and Shellfish Grower Advisory Committee Meeting, 18 March 1997 (Box 50)
    - Eastern Shore Vegetable and Shellfish Grower Advisory Committee Meeting, 6 January 1997 (Box 50)
    - Eastern Shore Vegetable and Shellfish Grower Advisory Committee Meeting, 17 October 1996 (Box 50)
    - Eastern Shore Vegetable and Shellfish Grower Advisory Committee Meeting, 5 December 1996 (Box 50)
    - Eastern Shore Vegetable and Shellfish Grower Advisory Committee Meeting, 17 October 1996 (Box 50)
    - Interagency Task Force on Plasticulture Meeting, 12 September 1997 (Box 50)
    - HR 40 - Plasticulture Study (Box 50)
    - VDACS Legislation, 2000-2001 (Box 50)
    - Strategic Planning Files from Don's Office (1) (Box 50)
    - Strategic Planning Files from Don's Office (2) (Box 50)
    - Strategic Planning Files from Don's Office (3) (Box 50)
  - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993
    - 29-31 January 1992, 2nd Annual Gypsy Moth Review (Box 51)
    - 5 February 1992, Meeting with Bill Porter/Visiting General (Box 51)
    - 12 February 1992, Meeting with Thelma Bland (Box 51)
    - 21 February 1992, Plant Pollination Advisory Board Meeting (Box 51)
    - 30-31 March 1992, National Food Policy Conference (Box 51)
    - 31 March-2 April 1992, Leadership Management Development Meetings (Box 51)
    - 6 April 1992, Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board Meeting (Box 51)
    - 28 April 1992, Marketing Exchange Group Meeting (Box 51)
    - 5-7 June 1992, Delmarva Chicken Festival (Box 51)
    - 11 June 1992, Seasonal Road Sign Meeting (Box 51)
    - 26-27 July 1992, Visit of the Governor of Enugu, Nigeria (Box 51)
    - 28 July 1992, Southern States and Central American Summit (Box 51)
    - 25 August 1992, House Agriculture Committee Meeting/VSU (Box 51)
    - 26 August 1992, SLEAC Meeting (Box 51)
    - 10-11 September 1992, Mid-Atlantic Poultry Health Council (Box 51)
    - 14 September 1992, Alson H. Smith, Jr. Library Dedication (Box 51)
    - 17-18 September 1992, Commissioner's Consumer Forum (Box 51)
    - 4-6 October 1992, 17th Annual SEUS/Japan Association Meeting (Box 51)
    - 18-20 October 1992, 7th Annual SEUS/Korea Economic Council Meeting (Box 51)
    - 13 November 1992, Governor's Symposium on Virginia's Economic Outlook (Box 51)
    - 20-22 November 1992, Legislative Train Trip (Box 51)
    - 30 November 1992, Commodity Appreciation Day/Virginia Farm Bureau (Box 51)
    - 1-3 December 1992, Agriculture Outlook Conference (Box 51)
    - 4 December 1992, Small Grain Board Meeting (Box 51)
    - 10 December 1992, Seafood Industry Meeting (Box 51)
    - 14 December 1992, Heritage Village Council Meeting (Box 51)
    - 6 January 1993, Trader Cattle/Farm Bureau Office (Box 51)
    - 14-15 January 1993, Virginia Pesticide Council Board Meeting (Box 51)
    - 15 January 1993, Legislative Informational Meeting/Farm Bureau (Box 51)
    - 19 January 1993, Retail Food Establishments Inspection (Box 51)
    - 11 February 1993, Farmers Market Nutrition Program (pilot) (Box 51)
    - 12 February 1993, Ghana Trade Meeting (Box 51)
    - 23 February 1993, Invitees to Proclamation Signing with Governor Wilder (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous, 1993
    - 4-6 March 1993, Virginia Food Processors Convention (Box 52)
    - 8-9 March 1993, Defense Conversion Conference (Box 52)
    - 12 May 1993, Safety Awards Program/State Police (Box 52)
    - 13-14 May 1993, Bartlett Tree Research Labs (Box 52)
    - 28 May 1993, Meeting: Pesticide Fees (Box 52)
    - 29 May 1993, Grand Marshall/Chase City Festival Parade (Box 52)
    - 4-5 June 1993, UN Conference on Food and Agriculture (Box 52)
    - 9 June 1993, Virginia Pork Festival/Emporia (Box 52)
    - 11-12 June 1993, 45th Annual Delmarva Chicken Festival (Box 52)
    - 14-15 June 1993, Governor's Budget Symposium (Box 52)
    - 15 June 1993, Hunger Forum Press Conference (Box 52)
    - 28 June 1993, Land Use Meeting/HJR 669 (Box 52)
    - 29 June 1993, Meeting with J. Nelson Stuart (Box 52)
    - 30 June 1993, Board Meeting (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983-1994 (bulk 1992-1994)
    - WIC Farmer's Market Nutrition Program (Box 53)
    - Population Figures, 1980-1990 (Box 53)
    - Administrative Process Act/Changes (Box 53)
    - Agribusiness Council's View on Lab Fees (Box 53)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council (Box 53)
    - Agricultural Banking/Funding Opportunities (Box 53)
    - 8-9 August 1994, Agency Strategic Planning Session (Box 53)
    - BE-LO (Box 53)
    - Certificates of Satisfaction/Partial Satisfaction (Box 53)
    - Correspondence, George Hobbs/Peanuts (Box 53)
    - 1992 Virginia State Legislative Guide (Box 53)
    - 21 May 1994, Meeting with Dr. Pearson/DCLS (Box 53)
    - List of Diversification Initiatives (Box 53)
    - 1993 Drought (Box 53)
    - Reports on Economic Development Enterprises/Economic Vitality (Box 53)
    - Energy Sources/Developments/Technology (Box 53)
    - Consolidation of Far East Offices (Box 53)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation (Box 53)
    - Farmers Home Administration (Box 53)
    - Report of Inspection Study Committees (Box 53)
    - Food Lion Controversy (Box 53)
    - James City Farmer's Market (Box 53)
    - 8 April 1994, Board of Trustees/Frontier Culture Museum (Box 53)
    - EEO Information/Infractions (Box 53)
    - 26-28 April 1994, Agency Strategic Planning (Box 53)
    - NASDA, 1983-1989 (Box 53)
    - NASDA, 1990-1992 (Box 53)
    - DCLS Advisory Board, 1991-1992 (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous, 1989-1995 (bulk 1992-1993)
    - 18 August 1992, Meeting/Marketing Exchange Group (Box 54)
    - Employment Procedure Complaints (Box 54)
    - 26 May 1995, Susta Board Meeting (Box 54)
    - Letters of Commendation/Congratulation (Box 54)
    - Internal Correspondence/Interest in Position (Box 54)
    - Virginia Agriculture Expo (Box 54)
    - Interview Information/Schedules (Box 54)
    - Resignations/Retirements (Box 54)
    - 2 May 1995, Lunch with Dr. Stephen R. Covey, Virginia Tech (Box 54)
    - Other Investors (Box 54)
    - 18 May 1993, Agriculture Nonpoint Source Initiative Meeting (Box 54)
    - 22 May 1992, Virginia World Trade Council Meeting (Box 54)
    - Memorandum of Understanding/VSU and VDACS (Box 54)
    - 2003: A Vision for the Future (Box 54)
    - The Governor's Report/Jim Longworth (Box 54)
    - Ground Water Management Act Advisory Committee (Box 54)
    - Sam L. Hancock/Hancock International (Box 54)
    - JLARC/Review of Virginia's Administrative Process Act (Box 54)
    - 28 January 1993, Kellogg Foundation Site Visit (Box 54)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act - Child Labor Bulletin (Box 54)
    - Department Logos (Box 54)
    - Mexico Trip/Report (R.E. Gomperts) (Box 54)
    - News Articles - VCES (Box 54)
    - News Articles - General (Box 54)
    - Virginia Partners of the Americas (Box 54)
    - Workgroup/Pesticide Management Plan (Box 54)
    - SMT Agenda Items (Box 54)
    - SLEAC (Box 54)
    - State Veterinarian Position (Box 54)
    - VDACS Strategic Plan (Box 54)
    - Project with St. Paul's College (Box 54)
    - Soil Conservation Service/USDA (Box 54)
    - Water Complaint - Madison County (Box 54)
    - Van Yahres - Information on Meetings/Farmers Market Opening (Box 54)
    - Timber Bridge Initiative for Virginia (Box 54)
    - Virginia Power/Special Farmer Rates (Box 54)
    - Virginia Sweet Onion (Robins Buck) (Box 54)
    - Holding - Wash. State Impact Center (Box 54)
    - VDACS Review Briefing, 1993 (Box 54)
    - Equine Medical Center Legislative Study Report (Box 54)
    - Virginia State University/Extension (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1996 (bulk 1992-1993)
    - Budget, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Budget, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Budget, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Budget, 1996 (Box 55)
    - FY 1995 Operating Budget (Box 55)
    - 1992-1994 Budget (3 volumes) (Box 55)
    - Financing Small Business (Box 55)
    - Emergency Fuel Delivery Letter (Box 55)
    - DEQ's Recruitment Efforts (Box 55)
    - Information on Scrapie Quarantine Policy (Box 55)
    - Mushroom Growing/Abandoned Mine (Box 55)
    - 23 August 1993, Agriculture Council Board Meeting (Box 55)
    - Alternative Agriculture (Box 55)
    - Documentation on Slowey Case by Billy Walls (Box 55)
    - 1992 A.R.E. Youth Scholarship Program (State Fair) (Box 55)
    - Dairy and Foods, Arthur Dell'Aria, Acting Director (Box 55)